celebrity-link.com 2003-06-10

# Celebrity Link: Privacy Policy

|  Celebrity Link is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information.

**Consumer Information**  
Celebrity Link does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, Celebrity Link does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by Celebrity Link is used for the purpose of improving our website for all our visitors.

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information for example when adding a site or subscribing to our newsletter. If this occurs, Celebrity Link will not give this information to a third party.

**Opt Out Procedure**  
If you voluntarily provided personal information and want this information removed, you can do so by sending e-mail to [privacypolicy@celebrity-link.com](mailto:privacypolicy@celebrity-link.com) stating what information you want removed.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use MaxWorldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). Banner ads are also served by [Adtegrity.com](http://www.adtegrity.com/). [Read Adtegrity.com's privacy policy](http://www.adtegrity.com/privacy.asp).

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

If you have any additional questions about Celebrity Link's dedication to consumer privacy, please contact us at [privacypolicy@celebrity-link.com](mailto:privacypolicy@celebrity-link.com). 

Copyright © 2003 [NetVision](http://www.net-v.com/). All Rights Reserved. Privacy Statement
